<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Matthias</title>
    <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Matthias</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Matthias Van De Velde</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://fpkmatthi.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Vulnhub - Brainpan</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/brainpan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/brainpan/</guid>
      <description>Initial recon Nmap Host discovery Before we do any port scanning, we need to establish the exact host (Or it would take a lot longer to finish). To initiate a ping scan, we use the -sn flag.
nmap -sn -oG nmap/host_discovery.txt 192.168.56.0/24
Output:
&amp;lt;snippet&amp;gt; Nmap scan report for 192.168.56.104 Host is up (0.00082s latency). Service enum Now we can launch a targeted port scan
nmap -sC -sV -oG nmap/service_enum.txt -v 192.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i3Talent</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/i3talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/i3talent/</guid>
      <description>Ofman quadrants    Qualities Too much Advice from others Dislike     Ambitious Dissatisfied Letting go Indifferent   Goal oriented Short-sighted Wide view Indecisive   Helpful Meddlesome Letting go Indifferent    Profession test Type: Doctor
Schein test  Being good at something (24 pts.) Independence (15 pts.) Social contacts (0 pts.)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proxmox Wake-On-LAN - alx driver patch</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/proxmox-wol/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/proxmox-wol/</guid>
      <description>At home, I use my old computer as a Proxmox server. To start my server from another computer in the same LAN or from a different LAN, I use Wake-on-LAN. Unfortunately, the alx driver is disabled by default since it breaks for some kernels. The bugtrack can be found here
 Download the patch  wget -O patch.tar.gz https://bugzilla.kernel.org/attachment.cgi?id=284877 Extract the archive  mkdir ./patch tar xvzf patch.tar.gz -C ./patch Add the PVE No-Subscription repo to the apt sources and install the current kernel headers  echo &amp;#34;deb http://download.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My ~/dotfile setup</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/dotfiles/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/dotfiles/</guid>
      <description>This method involves using a Bare Git repo. You can find the dotfiles for my daily driver here
Content  Starting a new repo Deploying dotfiles on a new system Final script  Starting a new repo Create a bare repo and an alias for git to work in that repo. Hide untracked files in config status. Put the alias in your shell config (e.g. bashrc). This way, you can use the alias when you open a new shell.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up my website enviroment</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/hello_world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/hello_world/</guid>
      <description>This write-up is about how I set up my repo, travis ci and docker container to work on my portfolio.
Content  Kick-off Docker Hugo Linking Github Pages Conclusion  Kick-off Create and open a new project folder
mkdir -p ~/portfolio cd ~/portfolio Docker Install docker (refer to the Arch Wiki ¯\(ツ)/¯ ) sudo pacman -S docker Creating docker image Alpine Linux is used as the base image
FROMalpine:latestRUN apk add --no-cache \  curl \  git \  openssh-client \  rsync \  bash \  hugoENV VERSION=0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i2Talent</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/i2talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/i2talent/</guid>
      <description>Competence test </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>i1Talent</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/i1talent/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/posts/i1talent/</guid>
      <description>DISC test 
The DISC model consists out of 4 temperaments(Dominance, Influence, Conscientiousness, Stability) and charts ones preferences, strong sides, communication and growth opportunities.
Perks of dominance:
 Loving competition and challenges. Goal-oriented and craves recognition for efforts. Aiming high, wants to call the shots and is generally inventive and ingenious. Mostly independent and individualistic.  Enneagram test The 2 types that stuck out the most were seller and perfectionist. According to the legend, these 2 types mean the following:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/about/</guid>
      <description>I am Matthias Van De Velde, a  years old student at Ghent University College. I am currently in the final year of my bachelor education in Applied Computer Science. Earlier this year, I got the opportunity to attend a 3 day CISA bootcamp, organized by ISACA.
After I have obtained my degree, I plan to persue the field of cyber security. Firstly, I&amp;rsquo;d go for certificates with more hands-on experience and later transfer to a more high-level view of the field.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fpkmatthi.xyz/contact/</guid>
      <description>How can I get back to you through email?
How should I address you?
How can I help you?

Submit
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>